const questionsData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    topic: "IDK",
    question: "why did all of my initial questionsData values vanish?",
    answer: "tell me, please",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    topic: "HTML",
    question: "What is semtantic HTML?",
    answer: "Element tags that are meaningful.",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    topic: "CSS",
    question:
      "Name two big differences between display: block; and display:inline?",
    answer:
      "display: block doesn't like neighbors. inline keeps to itself, and is happy with others around.",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
      },
  {
    id: 3,
    topic: "CSS",
    question: "What are the 4 areas of the box model?",
    answer:
      "1) Content, the inner portion. 2) Padding, what surrounds the content. 3) Border, this encases the above. 4) Margin, invisible space around the box.",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
      },
  {
    id: 4,
    topic: "CSS",
    question:
      "While using flexbox, what axis does `align-items: center` work on?",
    answer: "the main axis",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    topic: "Git",
    question: "Why is git valuable to a team of developers?",
    answer: "repos are in the cloud, and easily accessed by multiple members",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    topic: "Advanced CSS",
    question: "How would you describe accessibility on the web?",
    answer: "",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    topic: "Advanced CSS",
    question:
      "What are 3 different things you can do to ensure your website is accessible?",
    answer: "1) Alternative Text. 2) Transcripts. 3) Keyboard crawlability?",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    topic: "JS",
    question: "How would you expain the concept of a variable?",
    answer: "",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    topic: "JS",
    question: "What is the purpose of using functions in code?",
    answer: "",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    topic: "JS",
    question: "How do you access a key inside of an object inside of an array?",
    answer: "",
    completed: false,
    starred: false,
  },
];

export default questionsData;
